terrible terrible news everyone
i've lost my valuables seriously the
most valuable thing that i own
i've lost it and guess what it's not
it's not my shiny box of shiny things
this is not the most valuable thing that
i own
the most valuable thing that i own is my
b dubs head
i've lost it i usually keep it like
right here
in my box and i cannot find it it's not
in my in the chest anywhere i've checked
i've checked the box of heads
and i can't find it and i can't find any
other substitute b-dubs heads
this is a disaster everybody this is red
alert
this is the worst thing that's ever
happened on the hermitcraft server
fortunately for me bdubs is online so
we're gonna go and claim what's
rightfully
ours his face at this point b dubs is
kind of used to it but we're gonna go in
we're gonna go and we're gonna we're
gonna shock him and spook him
and we're gonna go and take his face
right off of him and that
unfortunately means i do have to
uh kill him so let's see if we can find
b dubs we'll have a little
quick mosey round the shopping district
see if he's anywhere there is uh there's
still plenty of
lulls in here no he's not here okay
right next next
port of cool is his base oh etho's here
didn't do the wiggle dance of friendship
b-dubs this house is the worst place
ever to find
b-dubs this way this thing is such a
maze
all right game face on everyone i you
don't understand
b-dubs his face gives me strength it's
the source of all my green powers
don't worry i've got a small payment for
him for his services
he must be so used to this by now right
b-dubs b-dubs b-dubs
if we catch him by surprise
we might be able to get this a little
bit
easier oh there he is he's on a horse i
can't get him when he's on the horse i
might accidentally get the horse
here we go we need to be sneaky sneaky
look how majestic he is right he's just
over the top of this hill i don't feel
like i can go for him while he's on his
horse
all i gotta do is i wait for night
i wait for night he's gonna go in his
bed
and it's gonna be the e by far the
easiest way of doing this
oh my goodness he's so close oh my
goodness he's so close
how far is it until night it must be so
close tonight right now
is he can he see me he
surely he didn't see he didn't see me at
all he might know that i'm here
but it is almost night time and if it's
almost night time
that means he's going to be camping his
bed
i hope he can't see me he's going to be
sleeping
there he is he's going to be sleeping
any second now
any second so predictable so predictable
okay here we go
this is gonna be one two
there we go we got it we got it
right we just need to go and pick up his
face
we picked up a bunch of things that we
didn't need
[Laughter]
hi i needed your
face for science right let's put his
stuff back
i will pay you handsomely there's a
there's six diamond ore
i don't know what else i accidentally
picked up i think i got everything right
i've got my new b-dubs head
oh that was such a perfect plan i am
complete
[Laughter]
[Music]
we're so handsome that's how we like to
start our episodes on the hermitcraft
server
stealing each other's face and paying
them diamonds for it now the big reason
that i wanted b dubs
head is because shenanigans are a foot
i need to go into the hep base we've
been waiting for them to finish
their build for a while and guess what
it's done
check it out the hep bass i've been
keeping an
eye the interior is completely done or
at least it looks like it i don't want
to get too close
but i'm going to cool together a team of
the bdubs heads
and we are going to go and infiltrate it
and see if we can get some of our
mycelium
back now we need the mycelium because we
recently purchased half of the shopping
district
and we don't actually have enough
mycelium to cover it it's actually an
enormous job
so we strangely need more mycelium
and so therefore i'm gonna call a
meeting with some of our top guys uh
there it is
wiggle dance friendship uh oh oh i
forgot that i had my beatles face on
yeah hey
okay right it's time to go to the base
all right
time to go to the base a bit
bit short on manpower today so
i've i've asked you guys here again
because uh i've got a little bit of
another little bit of a shenanigans plan
so last time we bought the shopping
district with the diamond throne
that we sold my cmt it's getting
complicated
the point is we genuinely need more
mycelium
to cover up our half of the shopping
district and i know who's got lots of
mycelium
they do the hep oh
is where i draw the line yes so exactly
why don't we go and heist it from them
yes you already got your game face yeah
i
[Music]
i lost my game face i had to go and get
a new one wait wait wait is that why
is that why there's a death by b-dubs
and chat from you
yes yeah it is i waited until night time
and shot him out of his bed
all right it looks like we are ready to
go there we all got our game faces on
yeah hold on
we might ready i'm smiling we may want
to ditch our
uh yeah we may want to ditch our main
gear i got just this thing
back up
the purple leather i'm glad we got some
use for leather
there it is hep hq oh my gosh it is
amazing it's huge
i've been waiting ages for them to
finish just so we can break in oh
man just so we can break in please
finish because we want to break in
excellent does anyone know how to open
this oh they got a they got an actual
door
they got an actual door wait not like
our vault that you just break through
this one actually has like a way of
opening what if well what if i just put
stuff in these barrels oh okay just any
random thing either well i put i put a
helmet in here and it vanished
oh i don't have it i can't reach through
but that might draw attention to us
yeah we want to it's probably a specific
key
i bet they're pretty smart i don't have
a key does anyone have a key
um no i have i have this map of mumbo's
face
try that no wait try that that might
work go ahead toss that and
it vanished oh no okay mumbo's face is
not the key
thing you tried all right let's try
must be busted right yeah i mean these
these windows look super old
uh no this this one's covered up no okay
i don't
i don't even know if i can land on it
this looks dangerous okay
yeah oh that you can go
oh i guess not okay it's a bit of a yard
sale there you go
you made it all right excellent uh
anything left behind there's my
beat-up's head
where's my face no no it's my face oh i
got it i got a doorway okay
nothing without my face
okay um i don't i don't think this is a
legitimate entrance
no we're kind of like stuck i think
we're behind the bowels
the bowels of the dessert factory
oh no wait wait wait what's this can we
go through the fire oh look at this guys
look at this oh
you burn a little bit but you'll be okay
can you guys throw it
parkour parkour did they not finish this
build
oh does anyone want to go for a minecart
ride it's
it seems terrifying this seems like
we're cheating we're like way
[Laughter]
is this a factory or is this a theme
park this is amazing
look at this place before the sars
though moo pop
chopped mushroom conveyor belt what the
heck is moo pop
their base is so much more fun than our
base
yeah they've been there use the
to make moo pop oh mushroom dry storage
and chop chop room
what are they making mood pop from
mycelium
what is me pop wait a minute wait a
minute so they have our mycelium right
now
and then they're using it to make moo
pop what i think that's what's happening
here
well i'm in i'm gonna hold my totem
though because i died accidentally
i don't know oh this is the this is the
door we're on the other side of the door
now
oh yeah this is the entrance
okay you got to do like a little tune to
make it open
oh i don't know how you open it from the
outside though
well the door's open for us to get make
an escape after we find what we can look
out for easy peasy
what about this is a vibe check should
we press the button uh
okay do you pass the vibe check i'm
gonna check out if i got the vibes
mm-hmm oh oh oh i don't know
you did not use that you did not pass
the vibe okay that's
that's glowing okay
oh no green doesn't matter no green
doesn't vibe either
okay we didn't pass the vibe check oh
man
dude what is moo pop i have no clue but
it sounds tasty
it sounds no it it sounds like
carbonated
oh what was the head i think you know
you activate something oh i'm sorry i
was pressing levers
oh why am i on fire oh something's
shooting at this
skeleton oh bro what what i'm gonna die
oh i did die oh i'm gonna die okay
now this is oh totem
glad they got this place rigged this is
okay
yeah they definitely have it rigged okay
guys let's take this let's take this a
little bit more seriously now because
i didn't quite realize this place was
rigged as heavily as it is
dude it's totally a drink it sounds like
fizzy milk which sounds
horrible this is a bad idea what do you
think this is a terrible 8
000 oh no are you okay
oh oh is there anything down there where
they keep the liquid for the moo pop
down here is there anything
anything here it's like a big reservoir
okay
dude it is it's carbonated milk that's
gross
ew they're making they're making drinks
out of
well i mean cows do make drink i can
sound silly
never heard of chocolate eating it or
something weird
i think this is like a big control panel
yeah i think we need to i think we need
to open that
giant wall that that i think the control
panel is
rigged hence yes it's very rigged
okay i'm kind of trapped in the control
panel now
oh uh tell me if these do anything
oh it's got a list of all the hell
members no dude okay no
this place is dangerous whoa
okay there you go i've lost my time
dude i don't even know what happened
okay don't touch the levers
but i've that's all i've been doing this
factory once made
okay a day apparently oh my gosh
that is impressive this is this is the
key to the
factory guard it with your life oh man
dude i got i literally got a key you
were reading oh you're reading about moo
pop
uh the history yeah note hep vault used
to be a moo pop vault
as such it is listed on the hermitcraft
register of historic places yeah
to open the vault place your certified
hip vault
beside this lectern one smart
okay i look i saved us from the skelly
did you kill him oh yeah nice nice i was
sick of him he was mean that's
that's 200 iq move right there okay so
i've got
i've got the key if i put it in are we
gonna die did i do something stupid
i don't know no i didn't yes
good job guys who's got their totems
let's get him in the mine cart let's get
him in the mine cart oh yeah yes
oh don't hit me don't hit me
don't hit me is he on me oh no he's
stuck on me so fast checkout is over
okay bring him through here bring him
through here come on come on he's not
gonna go in that
sure he is he sure he is he sure is no
no no no no no no oh
no he's coming around oh
okay i'm gonna get the mic back i didn't
bring anything to deal with a ravager
oh no no no no
security oh greedy's on you now no ether
get back here oh he's coming for me
oh it's going to take me a while oh no
we should have said our spawn yeah there
we go
i dropped one i dropped one okay we
should definitely set our spawn
heart and a half no oh no
man down man
this is going terribly is having the
time of his life probably watching this
they do they knew i i came up through
the chimney again
right here okay whoa okay this is a
that was a good statement
how did he get over that oh
oh this is not going we're just getting
demolished
at all what
oh they were so ready for it
he's on the bed oh no
he's on the bed oh you're you're oh
that's loop okay okay i come to your
rescue maybe
okay okay he's after me now he's after
me
get him out of here
[Music]
i've got the ravager trapped in the
corner but i need somebody to come up
and
put the box behind him i've cracked it i
don't know what i did but i cracked it
okay just spam it right get your get
your game face on we're we're back in
business
okay where is the ravager uh in the main
room in the back corner
back into the left okay there it is okay
and um if i go if i go near him is he
gonna i
think he's gonna stay on me but i'm not
100 sure
so just trap him in as high as you can
good boy
[Laughter]
[Music]
he keeps jumping up is the problem so we
need to like
you gotta get that stuff underneath them
though don't you get that blocks get
those blocks around him
they're not even coming to stop us
they've must have seen us die
yeah it feels like he's trapped if you
can
get it he can hit through box though so
don't get too close to him i was just
trying to get that i want
i want i got it i had to get my shovel
back
okay i think i got your pick too
yeah i think so oh all i got left is my
helmet in a pickaxe
we have bested you hep security yes look
at that yeah we totally uh
we got destroyed guys put your game
faces back on
my ceiling's back on the menu oh good
you found my game face thank you
that was the messiest okay let's just
regroup for a second here right are we
ready so
it's easy sailing from here on outside i
got any spare totems
oh i should have grabbed some oh okay
well hopefully that was the last thing
we need to face
he fell out of the roof i did not see
that coming no that was that was good
you gotta give it to him that was good
the best block on the lime concrete
that's got to be that's gross well yeah
but i mean
their best block has anyone got any
grass do you guys want to take
does anyone else want to place this
that's why i gave it to you
this feels like a terrible i think you
got agreed what
oh i heard cookies that's a lucky sound
okay
that's a happy sound okay the last
my ceiling what what have they done with
the mycelium
how is that the last one that's why they
haven't come to
that's why they haven't come here to
stop us it's not even here
they're because there's nothing for us
to because
they're like 70-something chakras we've
been like we've been triple bamboozled
what i worked really hard to get those
shulker boxes you tell me it's gone
what have they done with it well we
might as well should we take this
take this with us
what happened what was that oh
oh is it gonna wait a minute wait a
minute
nothing what was that noise
it's the mycelium look at it there's a
whole bunch in here
well i found the mycelium
i don't think this was supposed to
happen but i don't think so either
there's a lot of that they lied to us
though that definitely wasn't the last
mycelium because here's a bunch right
here
we only need enough to to cover the
shopping district so
yeah i think some of it got destroyed
but you know we can probably recover
quite a bit
all right let's take a couple shuffle
boxes and get out of here because i'm
done
dude i mean this is going to be wasted
right so we're going to despawn
can we just appreciate how many times
they got us
like i haven't checked the chat look at
that that's disgusting
it doesn't feel like a victory really i
think i think we've got to concede a
point to hep
yeah yeah we may have got some mycelium
out of it but we we definitely
we definitely lost our confidence
all right let's get out of here has
anyone got a sign can we leave a sign
for them
that'll do right
yeah this factory tour sucked that's
where i see them though
one night about something pretty good
i think that does sum it up all right
mission not really success point
point to them on this but we did get out
of there with enough mycelium hopefully
to cover the shopping district i have
actually started you see around like the
barge
there's uh i've started a barrier but oh
there you go yeah i got through
my remaining mycelium very quickly so
yeah the next the next task is to cover
this up which
i don't want to do right now well that
was a little bit insane
and ended up taking way longer than i
thought
but i don't want you guys to think that
i haven't done any work
this episode because after that i went
and i started well i say started i
continued gathering resources
for the big green barge
quest this is the thing that i talked
about last episode
and i've spent so many hours gathering
logs
gathering sand gathering everything
that's going to be part of the reward
and you might
think what are all these weird numbers
well these are the values of
each of these boxes so this is going to
be the prize pool
now the biggest value is here in each of
these boxes
two two eight and two to eight nearly
300 diamonds a box
and then tools for your mining sessions
these are actually really useful
if you're going mining for an extended
period of time or if you're going for
gravel and sand
mining it's very very useful so these
boxes
mega value plus everything else that
i've got going on
here now the problem is this has taken
me over a day to gather everything
and i'm still not done because it's 2v2
and because
the cost is 200 diamonds per person
it means the value needs to be somewhere
in the region of 800
to 1 000 diamonds 1 000 diamonds
is an insane amount of money
in the on the hermitcraft server and
therefore it's probably going to take me
longer than a day to set up point is
i've been doing a lot of work towards it
and i think i need to do i'm going to do
some quick
calculations we're going to find out
just how much value is here
wow okay so the grand total
the total value of all of this stuff is
diamonds that's not including the
shulker box value
and it's going on current shopping
district rates
so i think we can safely assume that
this is done
i have myself a prize pool so my next
task is to actually make
the quest that's probably the more
difficult thing out of everything i've
got to do
but this is definitely the most time
consuming so now that this is done and
i'll give you a little sample of what
there is to offer there's there is some
like junky stuff
granite diorite but there is some really
good stuff
as well b nest which are one of the most
rare items in the game
some logs logs sand dyes
rocket boxes wool big redstone
surprises some various things
blocks of quartz lots of redstone stuff
it's it's all
very useful blocks i don't think anyone
would be upset to win
all of this stuff so i'm gonna get
started
on getting a few of these mycelium
shulker boxes
and start to transform our side of the
island
so while i get cracking on this i'm
afraid that
is all we have time for in today's
episode
we have done quite a lot of stuff
and now i've got quite a lot more work
to do
so all there is left to say is thank you
very much for watching and i shall see
you
in the next episode where hopefully this
whole place
will be looking more purple
this is purple right yeah grey purple
good bye